badongo.com 2006-04-15

# Badongo - One Click hosting

BADONGO.COM Privacy Statement 

At , BADONGO, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. We offer services to internet users. We do not knowingly collect data from minors. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

BADONGO collects contact information for its databases. You may be required to provide personal contact data, such as name, full address, credit card and other financial information, and e-mail address to gain access to certain services. We may use cookies to monitor our websites' performance, and to collect IP addresses. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

BADONGO may use your contact information that you have provided to us for technical, administration, research and development, customer administration and marketing purposes. We may share or rent your contact information with third parties. We use customer contact information to send the user information about our company and promotional materials from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future email, newsletters, and marketing; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. Selection of an ad banner or link redirects you to a third party. The information practices of those third-party websites linked to BADONGO are not covered by this Privacy Statement. BADONGO is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party web sites and companies. 

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. While we strive to protect your personal information, BADONGO cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

Opt-Out Methods: 

1.You can send email to legal@badongo.com  
2.Call the following telephone number: +31 (0)433523653
